饶了我...
Please don't kill--
求你饶了我
Please don't kill me.
我女儿病得很重
My daughter is very sick.
闭上双眼
Close your eyes.
要是想活命 就按我说的做
If you want to live, do as I say.
246号 淘汰
Player 246, eliminated.
《鱿鱼游戏 3》
SQUID GAME 3
第一集:钥匙与刀
EPISODE 1
KEYS AND KNIVES
抬走
Take it away.
现在怎么这么配合?
Finally decide to be a good girl, did we?
不像你的作风
This is new.
我想了想
I gave it some thought.
反正他们都要死
Since they're going to die anyway,
拿他们的器官救别人的命也不是坏事
using their organs to save others
isn't such a bad idea.
这样想就对了
Good thinking.
我很高兴你总算想通了
I'm glad you finally came around.
我想看看
Show me around.
看什么?
Where?
看你们怎么干的
The workroom.
为什么?
What for?
我们现在
是一条绳上的蚂蚱了 不是吗?
You and I are
in the same boat now, aren't we?
我们之间可不能有任何秘密 对吧?
We don't want any secrets between us.
他死了?
Is he dead?
还活着
He's alive.
帮我把他抬到床上 快点
Help me get him on the bed. Quickly.
好
Okay.
来 抬到床上
Here. To the bed.
我在船附近看不到他
He's nowhere around the boat.
他昨晚喝了多少?
How much did he drink last night?
不到喝醉的程度
Not enough to be wasted.
我数了数里面的空酒瓶 数量可不少
I counted the empty bottles inside.
There were quite a few.
他可能到外面来吐 然后掉进了海里
He could have come outside to puke
and fallen in.
昨天晚上这船摇得挺厉害
The boat was rocking a lot last night.
莫非我昨天半夜
听到的动静就是这个?
Maybe that's what I heard
in the middle of the night?
你听到什么了?
What did you hear?
我听到外面有人说话
然后叮呤咣啷的
I heard someone outside, some thrashing.
那是几点?
What time was it?
大概半夜三点 对吧?
It was around 3 a.m., wasn't it?
对 差不多
Yeah, around then.
于是我就出来看怎么回事
朴船长当时已经在了
So I went outside,
and Captain Park was already there.
我们就该把大家叫醒 一起找找他的
We should've woken everyone up
and gone looking for him.
我们先搜索一下周围吧
Let's search the area first.
可是 黄警官
But Detective Hwang.
这里的海流很急
他很可能一夜之间就被冲远了
The currents are strong here.
He probably drifted pretty far overnight.
要是他喝醉了掉进海里
那肯定没命了
If he got drunk and fell overboard,
there's no chance he's alive.
你还有闲工夫去找一具尸体吗?
Are you going to waste time
looking for a corpse?
不是说要在四天内找到那座岛吗?
You said you have to find the island
in three or four days.
我们去最近的港口
再找个无人机操作员
Let's go to the nearest port
and get another drone operator.
走吧
Let's get going.
我们先进行攻击吧
Let's attack them first.
那我们也不能互相残杀啊
That doesn't mean
we should kill each other.
这样就正中那些人下怀
That's exactly what they want us to do.
为了大义就要承受小的牺牲吗?
A small sacrifice for the greater good?
就算现在会有牺牲
这次也一定要让游戏结束
Even if it takes a sacrifice,
we must put an end to this game now.
我们一起战斗 一起回家吧
Fight with us so we can go home together.
愿意跟我们一起去的人
请走到前面来
Anyone who wishes to join us,
please step forward.
你为什么不跟零一来 要带我来?
Why did you bring me instead of Young-il?
毕竟你是我朋友
Because you're my friend.
成先生
Sir?
哎哟 成先生
Oh, gosh, sir?
你还活着
You're alive.
幸好你还活着
Thank God you're alive.
你没事吧?
Are you all right?
其他人呢?
What about the others?
正倍呢?
And Jung-bae?
好好看看你扮演英雄是什么下场
Look closely at the consequences
of your little hero game.
奇勋
Gi-hun.
昨晚共有35名玩家被淘汰
A total of 35 players
were eliminated last night,
目前还剩60名玩家
and 60 players remain in the game.
截至当前 累计奖金总额为396亿韩元
The prize money accumulated
up to this point is 39.6 billion won,
每位参与者分得6.6亿韩元
and each person's share
is 660 million won.
现进行全体投票
以决定是否继续游戏
You will now take a vote to decide
whether to continue the games or not.
为什么唯独没杀我?
Why did you keep me alive?
为什么没杀了我?
Why didn't you kill me?
说啊!为什么!
Answer me! Tell me why!
为什么让我活着?为什么?
Why did you let me live? Why?
开枪啊 你们这些王八蛋!
Shoot me, you bastards!
对 开枪啊!把我也杀了!
Yes, shoot me! Kill me too!
为什么让我活着?
Why did you let me live?
你想让我怎样?
What do you want from me?
为什么没杀了我?
Why didn't you kill me?
你赢了!
You won!
赶紧杀了我!
So go ahead and kill me!
你赢了!
You won!
求求你了 直接杀了我!
I'm begging you, just kill me!
我们暂时回到港口了
We're back at the port for now.
他们想另找无人机操作员
然后重返海域
The plan is to find another drone operator
and head back out.
在游戏结束前
绝不能让他们发现这座岛
Don't let them find the island
until the games are over.
明白
Yes, sir.
喂 黄警官!准备好出发就联系我
Detective Hwang!
Give me a call when you're ready to go.
-好
-小心脚下
-Okay.
-Watch your step.
如果事情出了状况我该怎么做?
What should I do if things go south?
都杀掉
Kill them all.
那个警察也别放过
Including the detective.
现进行全体投票
以决定是否继续游戏
You will now vote again to decide
whether to continue the games or not.
投票将按玩家编号逆序进行
The vote will again be held
in reverse order of your player numbers.
456号 请投票
Player 456, please cast your vote.
若数到三仍未表现出投票意图
If you don't show an intent to vote
by the count of three,
将被视为弃权
your vote will be considered
an abstention.
一、二、三
One, two, three.
456号玩家放弃投票 按弃权处理
Player 456 forfeited his vote,
so it will be counted as an abstention.
接下来 448号 请投票
Next, Player 448. Please cast your vote.
放心 没人会吃了你 安心投就是了
We're not going to hurt you,
so vote freely.
对 随便投
Yeah, do whatever you want.
安心投 没人在看
Don't mind us,
feel free to vote however you want.
我们一共伤亡八名管理员
以及27名士兵
The casualties have been identified,
eight managers and 27 soldiers.
用劳工替换阵亡的士兵
Replace the dead soldiers with workers
尽快修复受损的设施
and repair the damaged facility
as soon as possible.
贵宾们很快就要到了
The VIPs will be arriving soon.
是
Yes, sir.
你是在哪里学的射击?
Where did you learn to shoot?
我听说所有朝鲜女孩都要服兵役
I heard women serve in the military
in North Korea.
是不是?
Did you learn there?
对
Yes.
你为什么越境?
What made you cross the border?
在那边饿得受不了了吗?
Were you starving up there?
还是说
Or perhaps,
你惹上了大麻烦?
you got into serious trouble?
你说过我们现在是一条绳上的蚂蚱了
You said we were in the same boat now.
那不是要多多了解下彼此?
Shouldn't we get to know
each other better?
等这一切结束后 我们单独在外面见
Once this is over,
let's meet up, just you and me.
到时候我会告诉你
I'll tell you then.
我不想等那么久
I don't want to wait that long.
这里有个很适合约会的地方
There's a nice spot for a date here.
你想顺路去看看吗?
Do you want to stop by?
我的事说来话长
It's a long story.
先让我看看手术室吧
Let me see the workroom first.
好吧
All right.
我知道楼下有个地方
I know a little spot downstairs.
你也会喜欢的
You'll like it too.
根据你们自由民主的投票结果
In accordance with your free
and democratic vote,
我们明天将进行下一场游戏
we will proceed
with the next game tomorrow.
各位辛苦了
Thank you.
喂 456号
Hey, 456.
莫非这一切都在你的计划之中?
Tell me.
Was this all just part of your plan?
你策划了一场叛乱 引诱人们出去
You staged a rebellion to lure people out
然后一举将他们全部杀害 对吗?
and had them all
killed at once, didn't you?
可他还一副那个样子
But he was all like,
“杀了我!”
"Kill me!"
纯粹演戏作秀呢?
Was that just for show?
这个人可真恐怖
Man, he creeps me out.
没错
That's right.
那些人没有像杀其他人一样杀了他
而是把他带回了这里
Instead of killing him like the others,
they brought him back here.
肯定是有原因的
There's definitely something going on.
不管怎样 你让所有那些 带红牌的蠢货都送了命
Anyway, thanks to you taking out the reds
and getting them all killed,
多亏了你 奖金更多了 我们还以压倒性优势赢得了投票
the money went up,
and we won the vote by a landslide.
各位 让我们用热烈的掌声感谢他
Everyone, let's thank him
with a big round of applause.
感激不尽!
Thank you very much!
看来你从一开始就是我们的人
I see you were one of us all along.
你个蠢货
You fool.
我怎么跟你说的?
What did I tell you?
你并非自愿来到这里
You're not here of your own free will.
是那些在你头顶盘旋的复仇之魂
将你引至此处
Those vengeful souls hovering
over your head brought you here.
听到了吗?
Do you hear them?
你耳边正回响着朋友们的尖叫声
Your friends screaming right in your ears.
任凭你怎么捂住耳朵都无济于事
You can cover them all you want,
but it won't help.
尖叫声只会愈发刺耳
Those screams will only get louder.
直到你生命的最后一刻
这些尖叫声都将伴随着你
You will be hearing their screams
until the moment you die.
- 放开她!
- 放手吧!
-Let go of her!
-Let her go!
没事吧?
Are you all right, ma'am?
状况怎么样?
How does it look?
能拿到些好东西
We'll be able to get some good bits.
慢一点
Slowly.
一、二、三!
One, two, three!
没事 别担心
Relax. Don't worry.
11号现在是我们的人了
Number 011 is one of us now.
这家伙状况不错吧?
We brought you a good one, didn't we?
这是她送给我们的礼物
That's her gift to us.
你怎么带她过来了?
Why did you bring her here?
既然都是一条绳上的蚂蚱了
We're in the same boat now.
大家相互认识认识不是挺好的吗?
Isn't it nice to get to know each other?
在我们之前的那些人都是因为
The ones who were here before us
ended up in deep shit
彼此不信任、互相隐瞒才惨遭不幸
because they didn't trust each other
and kept secrets.
但我们信任彼此
所以不应该有任何秘密
But we trust each other,
so there shouldn't be any secrets.
所以我们说好在这里不戴面具
That's why we agreed
to keep our masks off in here.
不是吗?
Isn't that right?
你就是11号?
So you're Number 011?
你知道我们因为你损失了多少钱吗?
Do you realize how much fucking money
we've lost because of you?
没时间说别的了
There's no time for that.
我们得快点才能按时交货 开干吧
We have to move fast to make it on time.
Get to work.
过来
Come here.
我从头告诉你流程
I'll show you how it's done
from the start.
这就是你的礼物
That's your gift right there.
他还活着吧?
He's still alive, right?
对 只是昏迷状态
Yeah, just unconscious.
好 那我们现在
就拆开11号的礼物吧?
All right. Let's open up
Number 011's gift now, shall we?
- 怎么?
- 住手
-What is it?
-Stop.
怎...怎么了?
What… What the…
放下手术刀
Put the knife down.
-好
-喂 到底为什么?
-Okay.
-Hey, what the hell?
退后
Step back.
你这是反水了?
You psycho bitch!
你个疯婆子!
想知道我为什么越境?
You wanna know why
I came down from the North?
我的指挥官跟你几乎一个德行
My commander was a lot like you,
于是我就爆了他的头
and I put a bullet in his head.
饶了我 我跟这些人不是一伙的
Don't kill me. I'm not with these guys.
我只是想挣钱才来
I just came here for the money.
救活这个人
Save this man.
他要是死了 你也没命
If he dies, you do too.
纯熙
Jun-hee.
红薯一直是你爱吃的
You like sweet potatoes.
成先生
Sir.
吃点东西吧 哪怕就吃一点
You should eat,
even if it's just a little.
我知道
Look, I know.
我知道你是想救大家的命
I know that
you were trying to save us all.
你只是想惩罚坏人 并结束这一切
You were trying to punish the bad guys
and put an end to all this.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我本该想办法
I should've found a way
把弹仓拿给你的
to bring back the magazines.
你没有什么好道歉的 贤珠
You have nothing
to apologize for, Hyun-ju.
都怪大虎
It's all Dae-ho's fault.
我看到了 我妈看到了 大家都看到了
I saw it, my mom saw it,
and everyone else saw it.
大虎来取弹仓 但就在要离开的时候
Dae-ho came to pick up the magazines,
but when he was about to leave,
他就瘫倒在了地上
he just sank to the floor.
而贤珠来取的时候 蒙面人闯了进来
When Hyun-ju came to get them,
the masked men barged in.
要不是我妈拦着
If my mom hadn't stopped her,
她也会没命的
she would've died too.
对吧 贤珠?
Isn't that right, Hyun-ju?
一味消沉并不能让任何人起死回生
This won't bring anyone back.
我们这些还活着的人
还要继续走下去 你说呢?
Those of us who are still alive
have to keep going, don't you think?
一定要吃饭啊 好吗?
Make sure you eat, okay?
你会口渴的 所以也要喝点水
Don't choke. Drink some water with it too.
哎哟 感觉他人都失了魂儿了
Gosh, he's completely out of it.
(11月4日 搜寻第四天)
NOVEMBER 4 - DAY 4 OF THE SEARCH
黄警官 睡了吗?
Hwang, are you asleep?
还没呢
No, not yet.
那既然没睡
Hey, since you're still up,
我们喝点儿酒 聊聊天儿?
can we talk for a bit over a drink?
好啊 请进吧
Sure, come in.
我就不喝了
No, I'm good.
哦 好吧
Oh, all right.
你想聊什么?请说吧
So, what did you want to talk about?
对
Right.
那个
Well,
是朴船长的事
it's about Captain Park.
你说他救了你
当时你差点淹死 对吧?
You said he saved you
when you almost drowned, right?
是的 我在一个岛上中枪后 掉进了海里
Yeah, I got shot on an island
and fell into the sea.
他把我救起并送到了医院
He rescued me and took me to the hospital.
那你还记得其他什么事吗?
Anything else you remember?
我醒来就在医院了
然后我妈告诉我是朴船长救了我
I just woke up at the hospital,
and my mom told me about Captain Park.
怎么了?
Why?
是这样
Well, the thing is,
我说我昨晚听到了些动静
于是出去查看 对吧?
I told you I heard some noises last night
and went outside, right?
是的 朴船长也听到了一些动静
Yes, Captain Park also heard some noises.
当时我没多想
I didn't think much of it at the time,
但他手里其实拿着什么东西
but it looked like
he was holding something in his hand.
什么东西?
What was it?
螺丝刀
A screwdriver.
谁在那里?
Who's there?
崔理事?
Choi, is that you?
是我 朴船长
It's me, Captain Park.
螺丝刀?
A screwdriver?
对
Yeah.
虽然很暗 但我绝对看到 他手里拿着一把螺丝刀
It was dark, but I definitely saw him
holding a screwdriver.
想想看 是不是很奇怪?
Think about it. Isn't that strange?
他为什么手里拿着那个东西?
Why was he holding that?
也许他在修理东西
Maybe he'd been doing some work.
可我记得他出来的时候
说自己正想睡觉
But I think he said
he was trying to sleep when he came out.
或者他为了安全起见抓了件武器
Or maybe he grabbed a weapon
just to be safe.
是吗?
You think so?
- 可是...
- 莫非
-But still, it's--
-Look.
你觉得无人机操作员的失踪
和他有关?
Do you think he has something to do
with the drone operator's disappearance?
我对这种事直觉很准
I have good instincts
for this kind of thing,
朴船长有点可疑...
and there's something fishy
about Captain Park--
他救了我的命
He saved my life,
而且这几年一直在帮我搜寻那座岛
and he's been helping me
search for the island for years.
即便现在也还是如此
He still is, even now.
我也知道
I know that.
我不是说他伤害了那位无人机操作员
I'm not saying
he did something to the drone operator.
我只是有种不好的...
I just have a bad--
你昨晚
也和那位无人机操作员喝酒了吧?
You had a drink with the drone operator
last night as well, didn't you?
是喝了 可喝得不多 就几杯
Well, yeah.
But not much, just a few drinks.
我们明天一早就出发
We're setting out early in the morning.
请回去睡觉吧
You should go get some sleep.
哦 好
Right, okay.
还有 从明天起
And starting tomorrow,
在船上不要再喝酒了
no more drinking on the boat.
好
All right.
第四场游戏即将开始
The fourth game will begin momentarily.
请按照工作人员的指示行动
Please follow
the instructions from our staff.
队长
Captain.
贵宾们到了
The VIPs have arrived.
你们现在看到的是
You are witnessing the fate
那些拒绝民主投票程序
of those who refused
the democratic process of voting
试图用暴力手段阻止游戏之人的命运
and instead attempted to stop the game
using violent means.
我们绝不容忍任何
We will not tolerate
any irrational behavior
破坏游戏规则的非理性行为
which attempts to destroy
the fair rules of this game,
此类行为
将按照我们的严格标准受到惩罚
and such actions will be punished
in accordance with our strict standards.
感谢大家的配合
We thank you again for your cooperation.
欢迎来到第四场游戏
Welcome to your fourth game.
本场游戏将分两队进行
This game will be played in two teams.
开始游戏之前 各位要先进行分组
Before we start the game,
you will divide into teams.
请依次从面前的扭蛋机里抽取一个球
Please take turns drawing a ball
from the gumball machine in front of you.
子弹没有击中任何主要器官或动脉
The bullet didn't hit
any major organs or blood vessels.
我给他缝合了伤口 但是...
I stitched up his wound, but…
但是什么?
But?
他失血过多
He's lost too much blood.
他需要输血 但没有血源
He needs a transfusion,
but there's no blood.
用我的血吧
Use mine.
你是什么血型?
What's your blood type?
O型血
Type O.
应该没问题吧
That should work just fine.
没关系
我们都还不知道要玩什么游戏呢
It's okay. We don't even know
what game it is yet.
要是敢耍花招 你就死定了
Any funny business, and you're dead.
接下来要进行的游戏是捉迷藏
The game you will be playing is
Hide-and-seek.
捉迷藏?
Hide-and-seek?
蓝队必须在30分钟内找到出口并逃脱
The Blue Team must either find the exit
and escape within 30 minutes
或者在时间结束之前避开红队的追捕
or stay hidden from the Red Team
until the time is up.
那抓人者呢?
What about the taggers?
就像我们小时候那样
Just like when we played this as kids,
我们只需要抓到他们就行了?
all we need to do is find the ones hiding?
红队 即抓人者 必须在30分钟内
The Red Team, the taggers,
must find members of the Blue Team
找到蓝队的成员并杀掉他们
and kill them within 30 minutes.
杀掉他们?
Kill them?
没错
That is correct.
红队必须找到蓝队并杀掉他们
The Red Team must find
the Blue Team and kill them.
若未能杀死任何对方队员
就会被淘汰
If you fail to kill any opposing players,
you will be eliminated.
这些人要杀了我们?
That is correct.
是的
这是什么?
What is this?
你们得到的物品
是通往游戏场内各个房间的钥匙
You have been given keys
to doors in the arena.
此钥匙可以开门
You can use that key
to go through the doors,
但门被打开之后就不能再锁上
but once a door is unlocked,
it cannot be relocked.
所以他们可以
找个地方躲起来 用钥匙逃脱
So they can hide somewhere
and use their keys to escape.
那他们也太容易赢了!
They have it so much easier!
- 没错!
- 比我们容易多了
-That's right!
-So much easier.
我们还要杀了他们才行
On top of that,
we have to kill those people.
而且只能赤手空拳
And with our bare hands.
没错 这不公平
That's right. This isn't fair.
他们又不会自己送上门来求我们干掉
It's not like they will just roll over
and ask us to kill them.
难道指望我们赤手空拳杀人吗?
How do you expect us
to kill someone with our bare hands?
我们理解各位的顾虑
We understand your concerns.
所以红队也有一份小礼物
That's why we've prepared
a small gift for the Red Team as well.
请打开盒子查看
Please open the box and check.
谢谢
Thank you.
这把刀可用于攻击蓝队成员
The Red Team can use knives
to attack the Blue Team.
但抓人者之间禁止用刀互相攻击
However, members of the Red Team
are not allowed to attack each other.
好歹给我们配个护具吧?
Shouldn't you give us
a shield or something?
给他们小刀却让我们空手乱跑?
You give them knives
and expect us to just run around unarmed?
就是
He's right.
你们也得给我们装备啊
You've got to give us something too.
就是 我们就只有一把钥匙
这不公平!
Yes, all we have is a key.
That's not fair!
可你们能用钥匙开门逃跑啊
But you can use the key
to open a door and escape.
没错
That's right.
只要躲起来就行
对你们而言更简单!
Just hide somewhere.
It should be a piece of cake!
-对啊
-就是 对你们而言更简单
-Yeah.
-That's right. You have it easier.
正大哥
Brother.
这不正是你所擅长的吗?
That's what you're good at.
像老鼠一样东躲西藏
Hiding like a rat.
游戏开始前
Before we start the game,
你们还有最后一次改变命运的机会
we will give you one last chance
to change your fate.
若有人对自己所处的队伍不满
If any of you
are not happy with your role,
可在游戏开始前与他人交换队伍
you may switch roles
with someone on the opposing team
并互换背心及道具
before the game starts.
什么?能互换?
What? We can switch roles?
没错
That is correct.
双方同意即可交换道具和背心
You can swap your items and vests
upon mutual agreement.
但在游戏开始后
But once the game starts,
严禁脱下或交换背心
removing or trading your vests
will be strictly prohibited.
请慎重选择
Please make your choice carefully.
各位 这位是新的无人机操作员
Everyone, this is the new drone operator.
很高兴认识大家
Nice to meet you all.
找他过来不容易 要好好待他
It was hard to get him here,
so treat him well.
-是
-Yes, sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
好了 先穿上救生衣
All right, put on a life jacket first.
不能再出意外了
We don't want any more accidents.
听到了吧?
I guess you heard?
听到了
Oh, yes.
你在哪儿?赶紧来 要出发了
Where are you?
Hurry, we're about to leave.
黄警官 你们去吧 我就不跟着了
Hwang, go ahead. I'm not coming with you.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
有件事我得去查清楚
There's something I have to look into.
你还在纠结那件事吗?
Are you still going on about this?
我的直觉一般都是对的
My gut feeling is usually right.
如果有所发现 我会打电话给你
在那之前小心行事 尤其注意朴船长
Mr. Choi…
崔理事...
好了 我们出发吧
All right, let's get going now.
-走吧
-好
-Let's go.
-All right.
你究竟是怎么回事?突然就冒了出来
What on earth possessed you
to show up here out of the blue
而且一大早就给我打电话
and get me out so early in the morning?
我忙得不可开交 累得不行
I've been swamped with work,
and I'm exhausted.
老大死了
The boss is dead.
什么?
What?
他死了?怎么死的?
He's dead? What happened?
说来话长
It's a long story.
等等 那你为什么不打电话给我?
Wait, then why didn't you call me?
就因为我现在走正道了...
Just because
I'm on the straight and narrow now--
不是那样的 他...
It's not like that. He was…
你知道
“石头剪刀布 收回一个”游戏吧?
You know
Rock, Paper, Scissors, Minus One, right?
-知道
-我们俩玩了这个游戏 然后...
-Yeah.
-He and I played it, and…
对 他只需要收回另一个...
Yeah. He just needed to minus the other…
算了
Never mind.
我们还是去喝点解酒汤吧
Let's just go have some hangover soup.
把话说完啊 然后呢?
Finish your story. So what happened?
开车 我路上跟你说
Start the car. I'll tell you on the way.
真是搞不懂你
I don't get you at all.
(武津室内设计)
How does someone die
by playing Rock, Paper, Scissors?
玩剪刀石头布怎么会死人呢?
How does someone die
by playing Rock, Paper, Scissors?
你们没人能活着离开这里
None of you can get out of here alive.
那我该...
Then, what should I…
唯有我 龙宫仙女
Only I, shaman of the sea,
能指引你们生路
can guide you to the path of life.
-我们相信你 女士
-我们会跟随你
-We believe in you, ma'am.
-We'll follow you.
天地神明啊...
Dear gods of heaven and earth…
从这里便能洞见彼方所有路径
I can see all the paths
in that place from here.
并非用双眼所窥!
It is not with my eyes I see!
天地神明
The gods of heaven and earth
正牵着我的手引路!
are leading me by the hand!
追随我者 可得永生
Those who follow me
shall continue to live.
敏秀
Min-su.
- 阻我路者 必死无疑!
- 你杀过人吗?
-Anyone who gets in my way shall die!
-Have you ever killed anyone?
喂 没时间了 如果你下不去手就换队伍
Hey, there's no time.
If you can't do it, switch teams.
你倒是挺会藏的
You're damn good at hiding.
敏秀 我昨晚到处找你
Min-su.
I looked everywhere for you last night,
可就是找不到
but I couldn't find you.
你藏在哪里了?
Where were you hiding?
你是害怕我吗?
Were you that scared of me?
你藏得很好 干得好
It's good that you hid yourself.
Well done.
那个臭婊子还以为自己是神奇女侠
That fucking bitch thought
she was Wonder Woman or something.
那婊子把我当傻子耍 她居然...
That goddamn bitch treated me
like a fucking idiot, and she…
你看到了吗?
Did you see it?
妈的 你看到了是不是?
Damn. You saw it, didn't you?
可你却像只死老鼠一样缩着
袖手旁观?
But you stayed hidden like a fucking rat
and just watched?
你应该帮她的 那个婊子喜欢你呢
You should've helped her.
That fucking bitch liked you.
敏秀
Min-su.
我喜欢你现在的眼神
I like that look in your eyes right now.
开玩的时候就保持这样 放开去干
Keep that look when you go in there,
and just go for it.
萨诺斯那个混蛋已经死了
Thanos, that fucking bastard, is dead.
咱们这个小团体的其他人都死了
只剩你我了
So is everyone else in our group.
It's just you and me now.
如果你也死了 我会很孤单的
I'll be really lonely if you die too.
所以这次做个男人吧 敏秀 好吗?
So be a man this time, Min-su. Okay?
你可以的 兄弟 敏秀
You can do it, my bro, Min-su.
敏秀
Min-su.
回头见 敏秀
See you again, Min-su.
纯熙 和我交换
Jun-hee. Switch with me.
你拿上钥匙
You take the key.
这样我们才都能活
That's how we'll both survive.
管好你自己吧
Mind your own business.
我会照顾好自己的
I'll take care of myself.
那怎么行?
How do I do that?
我知道你拿了刀也成不了事
I know you won't be able
to do anything with the knife.
少装出一副很了解我的样子
Don't act like you know
everything about me.
或许我不了解 但有件事我很清楚...
Maybe I don't, but I do know one thing.
你根本下不去手杀人
You can't kill anyone.
把刀给我
Give me the knife.
我会尽快干掉别人 然后就去找你
I'll take someone out as quickly as I can,
and then come find you.
我会保护你和孩子的 纯熙
I will protect you and the baby, Jun-hee.
你觉得杀人很容易?
Is it easy for you to kill someone?
只要
I would
能带着你和钱离开这里
杀光所有人我也愿意
kill everyone here if it meant
leaving here with you and the money.
为了保护我的孩子
我同样什么都做得出来
To protect my baby, I'd do anything too.
那...
Then…
你把我杀了吧
you kill me.
游戏一开始 我就去找你
I'll come find you once the game begins.
用刀捅我 然后出去
Stab me with that knife and get out.
那样你和孩子就能活下来
Then you and the baby can live.
把刀给我
Give me the knife.
我会跟别人换队
I'll switch teams
with someone else instead.
我们可以待在一起...
We can stay together and--
妈
Mom,
你膝盖不好
you have bad knees.
一进去
Once we go in there,
那些人就会举着刀扑过来
those people will come at us
with their knives.
如果我们待在一起
If we go around hand in hand,
两个都得死
we'll both die.
不 你下不去手的
No, you won't be able to do it.
你怎么可能用这个杀人?
How could you kill a person with this?
小时候打架 你就总是
Even as a kid, you always let other kids
像个傻子一样任人揍
beat you up like a fool
whenever you got into a fight.
你从没伤害过任何人 一次都没有
You've never hurt anyone, not even once.
那你呢?
What about you?
你能用刀去杀人吗?
Can you go and kill someone with that?
爸一直打你 可你从未还过手
Dad beat you all the time,
but you couldn't even fight back.
我来
I'll do it.
我尽力
I'll… try.
谢谢
Nice.
漂亮
十分感谢
Thanks a bunch.
那个 你愿意跟我换...
Excuse me, would you like to switch with…
听我说
Listen to me.
如果你跟我换队
If you switch teams with me,
我就跟你待在一起
保护你到最后 好吗?
I'll stay with you
and protect you until the end, okay?
但那样你也得杀人才行
But you'd have to kill someone too.
你能不能...
Will you just…
你就别管了
Just leave that to me.
我还是会跟你待在一起的
I can still stay with you.
请相信我 我会信守诺言的
Please trust me. I'll keep my promise.
好吗?
Okay?
妈的
Fuck.
怎么?你对我有意见?
What? What's your problem with me?
你为什么一直这么看着我?
Why do you keep looking at me like that?
你想把一切怪到我头上?
Want to blame me for everything?
我犯了什么滔天大错?
What did I do so wrong?
我们赢不了的
We wouldn't have won.
无论如何我们也赢不了的
We wouldn't have won anyway.
妈的 不要再这样看我!
Fuck, stop looking at me like that!
那不是我的错!
It's not my fault!
如果我们当时和选圈的那些混蛋打
If we had fought
the other damn side instead,
或许我们能赢
we could have won.
我们兴许能赢下战斗
然后赢得投票!
We could have won the fight
and then the vote!
都怪你
It's your fault.
他们都是因为
你那荒唐的计划才死的!
They all died
because of your ridiculous plan!
是你!是你杀了他们!
It's you!
You're the one who fucking killed them!
游戏即将开始
The game will begin momentarily.
蓝队 请准备进入游戏场
Blue Team,
please get ready to enter the arena.
重复一遍
Let me repeat.
游戏即将开始
The game will begin momentarily.
崔理事呢 他怎么没来?
What happened to Choi? He didn't show.
我之前跟他通了电话
I talked to him on the phone earlier.
他家里突然有急事
An urgent family matter came up.
这么突然?
All of a sudden?
是啊
I know.
也许他怕了
Maybe he chickened out.
他装得很强硬 还大声嚷嚷
People who act all tough and loud like him
其实最懦弱
are actually the biggest wimps.
这样也好
It's for the best.
他不过是个蹭吃蹭喝的酒鬼
He's just a booze-chugging freeloader.
妈 好好藏起来
Mom, stay well hidden.
我抓紧了事 然后就去找你
I'll get it over with
and then come find you.
我会找到你 然后保护你
I'll find you and protect you.
容植
Yong-sik.
每次你爸喝醉了 就总威胁要杀了我
Whenever your dad got drunk,
he always threatened to kill me.
但谁先死了呢?
But who kicked the bucket first?
是爸
Dad.
所以你真以为我会死在这里?
So do you really think
I'm gonna die in here?
另外 我还有个武器以备不时之需
Besides, I also have a weapon
for emergencies.
所以不必担心我
So don't worry about me.
做好你自己的事
Focus on yourself.
不惜一切代价活下去
然后我们一起离开这里 好吗?
Do whatever it takes to survive,
and we'll get out of here together, okay?
不要失言
Keep your word.
我一定会去找你的
I promise I'll find you.
靠...
Shit…
抓人者两分钟后进入
The taggers will enter in two minutes.
大家听好
Listen up, people.
以免被发现 大家散开去找出口
Instead of hiding,
let's spread out and find the exit.
谁先找到出口
就大喊一声告诉大家!
Whoever finds the exit first
will shout and let everyone know!
好主意!
我们互相帮助 一起活着出去!
Good idea! Let's help each other
and get out of here alive!
出来吧出来吧 早晚揪出小尾巴
Hide, hide, it's time to play
Don't let your hair give you away
出来吧出来吧 早晚揪出...
Hide, hide, it's time to play
Don't let your hair…
要不要合作?
Want to do it together?
什么?
Do what?
你觉得他们会轻易让你下手?
You think the blue vests
will just let you kill them?
当然不会
Of course not.
他们会拼尽全力反抗
They'll really fucking resist.
如果我们联手攻击 会容易得多
It'll be much easier
if we attack them together.
出来吧出来吧 早晚揪出小尾巴
Hide, hide, it's time to play
Don't let your clothes give you away
你没事吧?
Are you all right?
金子婆婆 纯熙
Ms. Geum-ja. Jun-hee.
跟我来
Come with me.
出来吧出来吧 早晚揪出小尾巴
Hide, hide, it's time to play
Don't let your hair give you away
-小心
-好
-Be careful.
-Okay.
我又不是要跟你“谈恋爱”
可以说就是“一夜情”
Just a one-night stand, so to speak.
你捅萨诺斯的时候
When you stabbed Thanos, you were
简直帅爆了
fucking awesome.
出来吧出来吧...
Hide, hide, it's time to play
红队 请进入游戏场
Red Team, please enter the arena.
联手吧
Come on.
开干!
Let's get it!
都怪你
It's your fault.
字幕翻译:郑伟
Subtitle translation by: Yoonjung Song